thefrugalgreenishmama.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Our Homemade Life

At www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com, we value our reader and your privacy is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com and how it is used.

**Comments  
**The Frugal Greenish Mamas a WordPress blog. Like other WordPress blogs, when you leave a comment on a post or page on The Frugal Greenish Mama, your comments are visible to other readers. This includes any personal information, such as URL or email address, that you choose to include when leaving your comment.  By leaving a comment or otherwise interacting, you agree that your comment becomes a part of The Frugal Greenish Mama and will not hold Amanda Fiveash or The Frugal Greenish Mama liable for any privacy concerns regarding your comment/interaction. By utilizing this blog, you agree to these terms. **  
**

**Surveys/Giveaways/Sweepstakes  
**The Frugal Greenish Mama may collect personal information for the purposes of surveys, giveaways, contests, or other blog features. This information will not be sold or rented in any manner. However, by participating in these items, you are agreeing that your information may be used for whatever necessary purposes in the administration of said surveys, giveaways, contests, and/or blog features. This includes featuring your first name and last initial in a blog post.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information.  IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com does not use cookies.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**DoubleClick DART Cookie  
**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL:  http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense

Commission Junction

Izea Media

Shareasale

Linkshare

Burst Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.thefrugalgreenishmama.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.  Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

The Frugal Greenish Mama has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thefrugalgreenishmam.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Note Regarding Internet Safety:  **I make no guarantees that The Frugal Greenish Mama will always be available, accessible, or virus-free. Circumstances can occur beyond my control, and I carry no liability for any damage to personal or business property due to use of The Frugal Greenish Mama or use of any of the links posted on The Frugal Greenish Mama.
